麦克斯  你猜谁要离婚了
Max, guess who's getting a divorce.
请告诉我是我们
Please tell me it's us.
不是  我们这段孽缘想断都断不了呢
Nope, we'll be together way past when we should be.
就像滚石乐队一样
Like The Rolling Stones.
要离婚的是杰森与薇诺娜·威廉姆斯夫妇
It's Jason and Winona Williams.
真的吗  我一直以为这一对会天长地久呢
Wow, I really thought those two were gonna make it.
我们说的是打女子网球的威廉姆斯姐妹吧
We're talking about those two sisters who play tennis, right?
没听说过他们
Never heard of them,
但我不认识的名人多了去了
but there are a lot of famous people I've never heard of.
比如偶尔会在电视上出现  还总念叨着
Like that guy who's on TV sometimes and he's always like,
"略略略  我上电视啦"
"Blah, blah, I'm on TV."
那是比尔·马赫
Yeah, that's Bill Maher.
反正他们是有钱又全球到处玩的上流人士
Anyway, they're rich, globe-trotting socialites,
他们要在我们甜品酒吧举行派对
and they want to throw a party at our dessert bar
来庆祝他们婚姻破裂
to celebrate the collapse of their marriage.
这年头都开始庆祝离婚啦
They celebrate divorce now?
那我妈错过了大概12场派对吧
My mom missed out on, like, 12 parties.
他们明天会来店里看看环境
They're coming tomorrow to see the place,
所以最好别穿你的"撒旦小队"T恤吧
so maybe don't wear your "Team Satan" T-shirt.
为啥  因为上面沾了污渍吗
Why, 'cause there's a stain on it?
这活儿能挣五千块呢  麦克斯
No, this could be a $5,000 job, Max.
我也有过能挣五千块的邀约啊
I was offered a $5,000 job once.
我说"想都别想"
I said, "No way."
现在想想  邀约我的就是比尔·马赫
Come to think of it, that was Bill Maher.
快看
Hey, look,
蠢丁笨熊
it's Saddington Bear.
外面的暴风暴雨可挡
Oof, unlike torrential rain,
但你的暴风吐槽难防
this jacket does not repel insults.
我得去检查排水沟
I have to go check the drains.
如果你在里面找到我的爱情生活
Oh, if you find my love life down there,
请帮我带回来
bring it back to me.
阿憨  台风不会来的啦
Han, the hurricane ain't coming, man.
我的身体能感知到灾难的来临
My body always knows when a disaster is on its way.
我预测到了97年厄尔尼诺现象
It predicted the '97 El Nino
以及我第三任妻子  戴安
and my third wife, Diane.
是真的  比如他感到胸痛的时候
That's true, and when he gets chest pains,
就表示天上局部多云
it means it'll be partly cloudy.
不  是表示我心脏病犯了
No, that's a heart attack.
呼吸急促才代表局部多云
Shortness of breath means partly cloudy.
我不盲目地相信厄尔能怪我吗
Pardon me if I don't just blindly trust Earl.
他投票给理查德·尼克松呢
He voted for Richard Nixon,
今年投给他哦
this year.
他会把我们从越南救出来的
Man, he's gonna get us out of Vietnam.
我才不要冒这风险
Well, I'm not taking any chances.
或许这话你们无法想象
This may come as a shock to you,
但这餐厅是我的一切
but this diner is all I have!
才不是呢
Not true.
你还有小短手和小短腿呢
You also have tiny arms and legs.
快看  是小黄人呢
Oh, look, a Minion.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
是我  我的芭芭拉  跟我的男保姆
Look, it's me, my Barbara, and my Manny.
我跟奥列格雇了他来帮忙照顾小芭
Yeah, Oleg and I hired him to help with Baby Babs.
你们知道吗  在波兰
You know, in Poland,
必需得切掉鸡鸡才能当男保姆
a Manny has to have his penis removed.
是啊
Yeah.
但在美国  他能留着命根子呢
But here, he gets to keep it!
我叫麦克斯  这是我第一次见到男保姆
I'm Max, this is my first time meeting a Manny.
我少女时期有过很多男性照"看"我
I mean, a lot of men watched me when I was a teenager,
但都是他们付我钱
but they paid me.
肖恩
Shane!
我花钱可不是请你来干站着
I'm not just paying you to stand around.
也随便给我们其中一个打奶嗝吧
Well, at least burp one of us.
是不是超萌超有爱
Isn't that the sweetest?
我老婆  我闺女
My wife, my baby,
以及一个做女人工作的男人
and the man with a lady's job.
你都不紧张你的男保姆...
You're not nervous your Manny is, you know,
长得超级好看
extremely good-looking,
而你...
and you're, well...
胯下有巨蟒吗
Hung?
而且他哪里好看了
He's not good-looking.
他的眉毛都没有连到一起
His eyebrows don't even meet in the middle.
苏菲不想请个女人是因为
Sophie didn't want to hire a woman because
我经常裸体走来走去
I walk around naked a lot,
而且我...
and I'm, well...
是史上最恶心痴汉吗
The grossest?
史上最臭变态
A stink machine?
姑娘们  我夫人在旁边看
Girls, my wife is here.
请不要再勾引老爷我了
Stop flirting with me.
麦克斯  你会跟肖恩去约会吗
Max, are you gonna go out with Shane?
他一直在盯着你呢
Because he's staring at you.
除非他是非常努力地看特价菜单
Unless he's trying really hard to read that sign.
我已经名花有主了
Uh, I'm already in a relationship
我跟兰迪在一起  你还记得吧
with Randy, remember him?
这么赞的高度  这么赞的厚度  这么赞的长度
'Bout yay tall, yay wide, yay long.
我知道长度有多赞  那是你的屏保
I know how "Yay long." It's your screensaver.
但是...  你们不是分手了吗
But, uh, didn't you guys break up?
好傻好天真啊  朋友
You are so naive, mi amigo.
这只是我跟兰迪之间的情趣过招
This is all part of me and Randy's dance.
我提议我们分手
I say we should break up,
他说绝对是分手了
and he says it's definitely over,
所以我们基本上还在一起啊
so we're still very much together.
我知道我未涉足情场有段时日了
I know I've been out of the game awhile,
但你这段话比穿淑女洞洞鞋还让人无法理解
but that makes less sense than dress Crocs.
我买那鞋的时候就没想问你意见
I didn't ask your opinion when I bought them,
我现在也没兴趣听你意见
and I'm not asking for it now.
而现在就到了过招中
And this is the part of the dance
他突然出现在我面前给我惊喜的桥段
where he shows up and surprises me.
靠  我真该穿上我的淑女洞洞鞋
Damn it, I should have worn my Crocs.
坏消息
Awful news!
我没办法修排水沟
I was unable to fix the drains!
因为我发现
Turns out,
我们压根就没有
we don't have any!
我们得自保
We need to protect ourselves.
我去外面填防洪沙袋
I'll be outside, filling sandbags.
想帮我的人  跟我来
Anyone who wants to help, follow me.
没人跟过来  是吧
No one's behind me, are they?
没有  你身后只有一个孩子拿着灯笼的影子
Nope, just the shadow of a child holding a lantern.
跟你说啊  肖恩
Oh, you know what, Shane?
我好无聊
I'm bored.
咱们走吧  回公寓去
Now, come on, let's go back to the apartment.
你可以在芭芭拉睡觉的时候帮我踩背
And you can walk on my back while Barbara naps.
正常男保姆都会那样做
You know, like mannies do.
再见啦
Bye.
走啊
Let's go!
杰森与薇诺娜人呢
Where are Jason and Winona?
他们得在暴风雨来之前到啊
They need to get here before the storm does
而且我头发开始起静电了
and my hair frizzes.
兰迪最好也在暴风雨来之前出现在我面前
Well, Randy better get here before the storm too.
有可能是他呢
Ooh, this could be him!
靠
Damn it.
唯一一次不想收到餐厅特价广告就来了
The one time I don't want a text from Chili's.
不过他们这个特价几乎跟白送没啥两样啊
Although they're practically giving away these sizzling fajitas.
杰森与薇诺娜  你们到啦
Jason and Winona! You made it.
我本来还担心  会不会发生什么意外呢
I was worried something horrible happened,
比如被困在暴风雨中
like you got caught in the storm
或是你们重修旧好
or you got back together!
得低于零度
I think it has to be below zero
火焰地狱结冻再说吧
for hell to freeze over.
我们很清楚  我们可是去过南极的人
And we should know. We've been to the Arctic.
他还杀了一只企鹅
He murdered a penguin.
那是意外好吗
It was an accident!
如果是动画片《快乐的大脚》里的企鹅
If it was the penguin from Happy Feet,
朋友  你得付出惨痛的代价
you'll pay for that with your life, my friend.
她是麦克斯
That's Max.
她觉得卡通人物都是真的
She thinks cartoon characters are real.
我叫卡洛琳·钱宁
I'm Caroline Channing.
而她真的觉得马修·麦康纳
And she thinks Matthew McConaughey
真的很享受开林肯汽车
actually loves driving a Lincoln.
不然他干嘛为这车子背书  他又不差钱
Why would he endorse that? He doesn't need the money.
就是这样
End of story.
这里好有爱啊
This place is so cute.
几乎跟婆罗洲的小泥屋一样有爱
Almost as cute as the mud hut in Borneo
就是我意识到自己不爱你的那地方
where I realized I didn't love you.
那不是五年前吗
That was five years ago.
这么狠的台词何不留到敬酒时说呢
Okay, maybe save that for the toast?
这里是我们正在设计的一些主题饮品
Here's some of the themed drinks we're working on.
就快单一[身]麦芽苏格兰威士忌
Almost Single Malt Scotch.
负心薄荷巧克力饼干碎一口酒
Resent-Mint Chocolate Chip Cookie Shooters.
还有正在商议的
Still debating the
"弄死兰"人就简单多了酒
"Tequila" Him Would Have Been Easier shots.
虽然很不想结束这次会面
Oh, hate to break this meeting up,
但我男人来了  快滚吧
but I think my boyfriend's here.
他不喜欢在我工作的时候打扰我啦
Yeah, he doesn't like to bother me when I'm working.
或许我该趁天气变更恶劣之前先走
Well, maybe I should get going before the weather gets too bad.
我得去赴一场五年前早该去赴的约
I have a date I should have gone on five years ago.
我敢打赌压根没下雨
Oh, I bet it's not even raining.
你们看  毛毛雨而已
See? Just a little sprinkle.
你还穿了胸罩啊
You wear a bra?
台风正朝着威廉斯堡迎头而来
The hurricane is headed right for Williamsburg.
街上帽子被吹得满天飞
Fedoras are blowing down the streets.
精酿啤酒洒得满地都是
Craft beers are spilling everywhere.
独立音乐乐团练习取消
And indie bands are cancelling practice.
抱歉  姑娘们  夏奇拉错了
Sorry, girls, I guess Shakira was wrong.
我的屁股说谎了
My hips do lie.
这就是为什么兰迪还没来
This explains why Randy isn't here yet.
他估计是被困暴风雨里了
He's probably stuck in the storm.
麦克斯  你这是妄想症发作啊
Max, you're being delusional.
我能看出来是因为我就妄想症很严重
And I know that because I'm delusional.
阿憨  我得回家了
Han, I have to get home.
苏菲跟男保姆在家独处
Sophie's alone with the Manny
而每当天气不好  她就特别性奋
and she gets turned on by bad weather.
是真的
It's true.
上次下雪  她还跟我亲热了一番
Last time it snowed, we made out a little bit.
她最爱的色情片就是《完美风暴》[灾难片]
Her favorite porno is The Perfect Storm,
哪怕片中女配角的烂波士顿口音都阻止不了
even with Diane Lane's horrible Boston accent.
奥列格  别啊  太危险了
Oleg, no, it's too dangerous.
对啊  阿憨  快陪他去
Yeah, it is. Han, go with him.
但偏偏  风渐渐  把距离吹得好远
Even the wind pushes Oleg away.
我上次被"吹"得那么惨还是
That's my worst experience being blown
在女厕所里"那里"卡在干手机里
since I got caught in the hand dryer in the ladies' washroom.
糟糕  大家快进冰库
Oh, no. Everyone into the walk-in.
看来我们要被困在这里了
Well, I guess we're stuck here.
又一次被当人质挟持了
Another hostage situation.
就像我们的蜜月
Just like our honeymoon.
少来  你明明喜欢德黑兰
Oh, you loved Tehran.
你们想看看菜单的样本吗
So do you guys want to see a sample menu?
麦克斯点个火柴  方便人家看到
Max, light a match so they can see.
等我一下  我在搜刮提款机
Give me a sec. I'm looting the register.
抱歉  下意识反应
Sorry, it's a reflex.
我们应该在食物过期前全吃完吗
Should we eat all the food before it expires?
到期日两年前
Two years ago.
这里是整栋楼里最安全的地方了
This is the safest place in the building.
这里曾是我的包礼物小套房
This used to be my gift-wrapping suite.
我是说我的男人窝啦
I mean, man cave.
我是坐到了一袋土豆上吗
Am I sitting on a sack of potatoes?
不是  是我肥大的前列腺
Nope. Just my prostate.
非常抱歉造成你们的不便
So sorry for the inconvenience.
要不我请你们吃点斑豆
Can I offer you some pinto beans?
来桶卷心菜沙拉
A tub of slaw?
还是老鼠骨架
Mouse skeleton?
这的确让我回想起那时候在雨林
Well, it does remind me of that time in the rainforest
我们偷了当地部落的食物
when we stole that tribe's food
结果被他们绑着生殖器吊起来
and they hung us up from our genitals.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
那天你看起来超可爱
Oh, you looked so cute that day.
整个人被倒挂着  还大叫
All upside down and screaming.
别说了
Stop.
"倒挂[69]还大叫"
"Upside down and screaming"?
真是够了
Oh, that's it.
我要跟苏菲视频确保
I'm FaceTiming Sophie to make sure
她的"风口"紧紧关闭
her storm door is sealed shut.
苏菲
Sophie.
我第一次超感激你穿戴整齐
For once I'm grateful you have all your clothes on.
尽管...
Although...
别分心  奥列格
stay focused, Oleg.
奥列格
Hey, Oleg.
我们没事  我给芭芭拉念她的星座运势呢
Yeah, we're fine, I was just reading Barbara her horoscope.
她马上要知道谁才是她真正的朋友了
Now she's about to find out who her true friends are.
对了  告诉姑娘们我们把栗宝带进屋了
Yeah, oh, and tell the girls that we brought Chestnut in.
"我们"
"We"?
他的上衣呢
What happened to his shirt?
栗宝的吗
Chestnut's?
我脱掉了  他身子很暖啊
Well, I took it off. He was warm.
不  苏菲  是男保姆的上衣
No, Sophie, the Manny.
他的奶头正跟我对视呢
His nipples are staring at me.
那你觉得他的上衣怎么了
Well, what do you think happened to it?
他把红酒洒到...奥列格  我要挂了
He spilled his wine... hey, Oleg, I gotta hang up.
我们得关窗户了  外面有一场完美风暴
We gotta close the windows. It's a perfect storm out there.
好啊  我也要上马
Yeah, I think I am gonna get up there
跟你一起  不做任何"防护措施"[无马鞍]
on that horse bareback with you.
"完美风暴"
"Perfect storm"?
完了  这太糟糕了
Oh, no, this is terrible.
红酒  暴风雨
There's wine. There's a storm.
外加一匹马
There's a horse in the mix.
开搞的可能性无极限啊
The sexual possibilities are dizzying!
红酒
Wine?
这倒提醒我了
Ooh, that reminds me.
抱歉  我们红酒喝完了
Oh, sorry. We're out of wine.
谁想来一杯果汁加伏特加
Who wants a Capri Sun and vodka?
重问一遍
Scratch that.
谁会不想来一杯喝果汁加伏特加
Who doesn't want a Capri Sun and vodka?
我该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
我的应急背包里有旅行版组词游戏
I have travel Scattergories in my emergency backpack.
扔个F来"feng"狂玩一下?
Perhaps we roll an F for fun?
扔个阿憨出门来疯狂玩一下如何
Perhaps we roll you outside for fun?
原来众志成城共度危机也不过如此
Oof, so much for the community coming together during a crisis.
这里的解手政策是什么
Oh, what's the bathroom policy around here?
随便哪儿都行吗
Just go anywhere?
完了完了  这下不妙
Oh, no, no, this is not good.
我的餐厅现在比苏菲还"操"蛋了
My diner is more screwed than Sophie right now.
太快开这玩笑吗
Too soon?
抱紧我
Hold me!
先跟你说一声
Just so you know,
那根东西  真的是我口袋里的手电筒
that is a flashlight in my pocket.
我们要谈谈刚才发生的事吗
Are we gonna talk about what happened?
麦克斯  拜托告诉我
Max, please tell me they make
真的有非常非常小的手电筒
really, really small flashlights
而且还会自己动的那种
that move on their own.
你是想我骗你
Do you want me to lie to you
还是想我告诉你那是阿憨的小鸡鸡
or do you want me to tell you that was Han's penis?
卡洛琳和阿憨在那边真是打得火热啊
Caroline and Han are really getting at it over there.
这场暴风雨更让人欲火焚身
This storm is turning people on
简直完胜酒精和没自尊啊
more than alcohol and low self-esteem.
就连阿憨都尝到甜头了
Even Han got some action.
我不会一跟人牵手就到处说
I don't hold hands and tell.
或许我会  毕竟以前也没有过
Or maybe I do. This is kind of a first.
我感觉到了
I could tell.
你的大拇指到处乱窜
Your thumb was all over the place.
我希望那根是你的大拇指
I hope that was your thumb.
够了
That's it.
我不能冒险让苏菲独自一人
I can't risk Sophie being alone
跟那个巨根男保姆待在一起
with the Elephant Manny any longer.
在这种坏天气下  他这种2分男都能变5分
Even a 2 like him looks like a 5 in this bad weather,
而苏菲喜欢5开头的东西
and Sophie has a thing for 5s.
如果我不幸牺牲了  麦克斯
If I die, Max,
你知道我的葬礼该请什么样的脱衣舞娘
you know what strippers I want at my funeral.
知道  跟我葬礼的理想型一样
Yep, same ones I want at mine.
我的葬礼要请风笛[人名]
I want Bagpipes at my funeral.
她等着你打给她哟
She'll be expecting your call.
性张力越来越强了哦
The sexual tension is rising.
越来越向"我们会还是不会呢"这问题靠近了
This is turning into a real "Will we or won't we?"
我们不会
We won't.
我们可不能啊
We can't!
你知道我一直想做什么吗
You know what I've always wanted to do?
开一个"复合"派对吗
Have a "Getting back together" party?
价格一样  就音乐少播点阿黛尔的歌
Same price, less Adele on the playlist.
不
No.
你懂的  我们该...
You know. We should...
驱车穿越叙利亚
Drive through Syria!
叙利亚
Syria?
是新开的那家中东快餐店吗
Is that a new Middle Eastern fast-food place?
以色列"茄"万别让我吃酱
Baba ghano-thank-you.
叙利亚感觉很不错
Syria sounds beautiful.
让我们帮你们办个欢送派对吧
Let us throw your going-away party.
还是有生日派对  毕业派对
And birthdays coming up? Graduations?
15岁成年派对  为派对而办的派对呢
Quinceaneras? Just 'cause?
为何要差点死在叙利亚
Why almost die in Syria
我们现在明明可以
when we could be out there right now
冲出去差点死在狂风暴雨里
almost dying in a hurricane?
这才是我家人逼着我娶她的女人啊
Oh, there's the woman my family forced me to marry.
我们在这里的每一秒都是在浪费
Every second we're in here is second we're not
我们能被外面倒下的电线电死的机会
risking getting electrocuted by downed power lines.
各位有缘再见
We'll see you guys later.
那个...我们也承接丧礼啊
Wha... we do funerals.
还有守灵和七日服丧期[犹太教]
Wakes, shivas, too.
跟你们当年的绑匪宣传下
Tell your captors.
真是难以置信
Unbelievable.
我果然不善处于感情
I'm so bad at relationships,
甚至连离婚都能搞砸
I can't even make a divorce work.
我教你几招吧
I'll give you some pointers.
规则一  跟她的大嘴巴姐妹上床
First rule, have sex with her big-mouthed sister.
我要看看兰迪有没有在他的快拍上
I'm gonna see if Randy posted anything on Snapchat
透露有关他的行程
about his travels.
我知道你在想什么  你绝对是错的
I know what you're thinking, and you're wrong.
他肯定不在洛杉矶享受日光浴
He is not in LA, enjoying the sunshine.
我在阳光灿烂的洛杉矶
Hey, I'm here in sunny LA,
准备带我的狗狗去散步
just about to take my dog for a walk.
人们都在说我们俩越长越像了
You know, people are saying we're starting to look alike.
你们怎么看
Thoughts?
因为说实话  我不这么觉得
Because to tell you the truth, I don't really see it.
虽然我比之前更常在消防栓上尿尿
Although I have been peeing on fire hydrants more than usual.
算了
You know what?
我打给他好了
I am calling him.
他希望我打给他
He wants me to.
你也看见他狗鼻子上的表情啦
You saw the look on his snout.
你的行为比我还错乱
You're acting more mixed-up than me.
昨天我在一台自动提款机上点了个汉堡呢
And yesterday I ordered a cheeseburger from an ATM.
不得不说  味道还不赖
And I gotta say, it wasn't bad.
他不接  直接转去语音信箱了
He's not answering, and it's going straight to voicemail.
或许快拍搞错了
Maybe Snapchat got it wrong
他已经在飞机上了
and he's on a plane.
他很可能屏蔽你电话了
He probably blocked you.
对吧  宝贝儿
Right, baby?
把你电话给我
Give me your phone.
你好
Hello?
打通了  他接了
It went through and he answered.
因为那不是我的电话号  他果然屏蔽我了
'Cause it wasn't my phone. He did block me.
麦克斯  很遗憾
Max, I'm sorry.
我们真的彻底分手了
We're really broken up.
别太难过
Don't feel too bad.
就我刚才看  他长了一张白痴狗脸
From what I saw, he had kind of a dog face.
我的臀部感知到暴风雨已经结束了  各位
My hips think that the storm is over, y'all.
你干嘛不去看看有没有洪水  老头
Why don't you go check for flooding, old man?
就像你当年帮诺亚那样
Just like you did for Noah.
抱歉  是我新恋情的让我自信膨胀了
Sorry, that's the cockiness of my new relationship talking.
我们都该走了
We should all go.
反正我们谁都没有任何活下去的理由
None of us have anything left to live for anymore anyway.
不好意思  我可是有大把...
Uh, excuse me, I have plenty...
好吧  你说得对  走吧
okay, you're right, let's go.
太棒了  餐厅没事
Yes! Yes, it's okay.
我猜台风在点评网上查过咱们
I guess the hurricane looked us up on Yelp
然后觉得应该避而远之
and stayed the hell away.
在暴风雨中毫发无损
It survived the storm!
我的餐厅还活着
My diner's alive.
是啊  它的某些"鼠"性刚还在厨房追我呢
Yeah, parts of it have chased me around the kitchen.
我超爱你的搞笑
I love how you're funny.
暴风雨走了  我身体的感知是对的
The storm is gone. My body got it right.
现在如果它能自己供血就好了
Now, if it could only pump blood on its own.
不错嘛  奥列格也没死
Great. Oleg survived too.
这场台风逊爆了
This hurricane sucked.
我回了家
I made it home,
可苏菲和男保姆都走了
but Sophie and the Manny were gone.
我可以从栗宝的眼神
And I could tell by the look in Chestnut's eyes
和他的鬃毛上的红酒看出
and the wine on his mane
他们不会回来了
that they're not coming back.
奥列格  你在这里啊
Oh... Oleg, you're here!
苏菲
Sophie,
你来了
you're here.
我好担心你  发生什么事了
Oh, I was so worried. What happened?
我的西班牙油条吗
To my churro?
是啊  都弄湿了
Well, yeah, it got wet.
奥列格
Oh, Oleg,
我不想刮台风的时候没有你在身边
I didn't want to be in the hurricane without you.
我也不想别人上你的时候
And I didn't want anyone to be in you
没有我在身边
without me.
别傻了  我们现在是一家人
Don't be silly. We're family now.
再说了  暴风雨让我欲火焚身
Plus, the storm got me all horned up.
我承认
Confession:
让我湿身的不只是暴风雨
I'm not just wet from the storm.
老天
Oh, my God,
这家伙是不是特会见缝插棒啊
does this guy always know what to say or what?
奥列格  我们回家吧
Oh, Oleg, let's go home.
我爱幸福结局
I love happy endings.
如果芭芭拉睡着了
Oh, well, if Barbara's sleeping,
没准在回家的路上我就能让你"性福"一把哦
I might be able to give you one on the way home.
卡洛琳
Caroline,
我们得谈谈刚在里面发生的事
we need to talk about what happened in there.
好的  但我非得在场吗
Okay, but do I have to be here?
听着  我一直在想有时候
Look, I've been thinking that sometimes
极端天气会让你做一些疯狂的事
crazy weather makes you do crazy things.
对  我刚听苏菲和奥列格瞎扯了
Yeah, I just listened to Sophie and Oleg talk
大概一个小时吧
for like an hour.
我...我想说的是
I... I guess what I'm trying to say is
我们结束了
we're dones-ville.
阿憨
Han.
不不不
No, no.
别开口求我
Don't beg.
跟你分开已经够难了
This is hard enough as it is.
但是...
But...
打起精神来
keep that chin up.
你会找到对的人
You'll find someone.
我建议你上网找
I recommend the Internet.
多谢  阿憨
Thanks, Han.
其实还挺有意思  虽然压根就没开始过
It was fun while it never started.
麦克斯  我不喜欢看到你这样
Max, I hate seeing you like this.
或许兰迪屏蔽你的唯一原因是...
You know what? Maybe Randy only blocked you because...
因为他不想毁掉给我的惊喜
Because he didn't want to ruin the surprise of him
他要来这里见我了
coming here to see me?
好吧  当然是啊
All right. Yep. Sure.
我再去看看他的快拍
I'm gonna check his Snapchat again.
等会吧  麦克斯  先去抱抱我们的甜品吧
Not now, Max. Let's go hug our dessert bar.
它一定吓坏了
It was probably so scared.
我在跑因为我迟到了
Hey! I'm running 'cause I'm late.
我得去纽约...
Gotta get to New York...
这下好  他没讲完就断了
Great, his story cut off.
但你说对了
But you were right!
深表怀疑
I was?
画面动了
Ooh, it unfroze.
交响乐团在好莱坞露天剧场的演出
Philharmonic at the Hollywood Bowl.
就这样吧
Well, that's it.
他不会来纽约了
He's not coming to New York.
我得面对现实
I have to face reality.
他约了好朋友菲尔在洛杉矶打保龄球
He's bowling in LA with his buddy Phil.
我的上帝
Oh, my God!
很扯  对吧
Cray, right?
我都不知道兰迪喜欢打保龄球
I didn't even know Randy liked bowling.
不  麦克斯  你看
No, Max, look!
那树是新种的吗  还是一直在那里的
Is that tree new or has it always been there?
我知道树上的保险套肯定不是
I know the condom stuck to it hasn't.
那个破餐厅居然没事  而我们美丽的甜品酒吧
The diner is fine, but our beautiful dessert bar
却被台风袭击了
gets hit by the hurricane?
可是...
But...
你的头发现在看起来挺好啦
your hair looks good right now.
才"挺好"吗
Just "Good"?
我要打给阿憨
I'm calling Han.
我现在竟然觉得我需要他
I weirdly feel like I need him now.
直接转去语音信箱了
It's going straight to voicemail.
阿憨  我刚打给你呢
Han! I was just trying to call you.
没错  我屏蔽你了
Yeah, I blocked you.
我现在真的不想再谈那事
I just can't go there right now.
卡洛琳  别哭
Caroline, don't cry.
我们有保险的不是吗
We have insurance. Right?
你说的话我百分百都没听啦
I don't listen to 100% of what you say.
我们会没事的
We'll be fine.
我只是觉得屏蔽别人这事太伤人了
I just think blocking a person is mean.